Finding Aid for Susan Wineberg papers, 1965-2009
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Ann Arbor Historic Preservation and Development Materials
  - Subject Files
    - Groves, William (Box 24)
    - Gunn, Dr. Moses and Jane (Box 24)
    - Hathaway, Mary (Box 24)
    - Katzman 1966 (Box 24)
    - Kimball, Fiske, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Latimer, Ralph (Box 24)
    - Lorch, Emil (Box 24)
    - Pieper, Louisa (Box 24)
    - Railroad Jack (Box 24)
    - Ryan, Milo (Box 24)
    - Schmiedeke, Denis (Box 24)
    - Scheleper, Vandaworker (Box 24)
    - Shackman, Grace (Box 24)
    - Apparow, Gio (Box 24)
    - Stegman (Box 24)
    - Stephenson, O. W. (Box 24)
    - 712 East Ann, 3 folders (Box 24)
    - James/Breiholz (Box 25)
    - 712 East Ann Guests and Tenants (Box 25)
    - 712 East Ann on HGTV (Box 25)
    - 712 East Ann Photos (Box 25)
    - 1001 Broadway (Box 25)
    - 220 N. Fifth (Box 25)
    - 803 E. Kingsley (Box 25)
    - 602 Lawrence (Box 25)
    - 604 W. Liberty (Box 25)
    - 307 N. State (Box 25)
    - 315 N. State (Box 25)
    - S. Fifth Ave., 400 block (Box 25)
    - 202 S. Division 2008 (Box 25)
    - Broadway Village (Box 25)
    - Glen Ann 6-8 2007-2008, 3 folders (Box 25)
    - Frieze Building 2004-2005, 2007-2008, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Frieze/North Quad, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - 320 E. Liberty (Box 26)
    - 372 E. Liberty (Box 26)
    - Historic District Commission Network (Box 26)
    - Historical Society of Michigan (Box 26)
    - Saarinen Chapter (Box 26)
    - State Historic Preservation Plan (Box 27)
    - Michigan Historical Center (Box 27)
    - Michigan and Preservation (Box 27)
    - Michigan Historical Preservation Network (Box 27)
    - R. S. Gerganoff (Box 27)
    - Gardens: Clubs, Business, etc. (Box 27)
    - Michigan: Preservation Consultants (Box 27)
    - NBD Community Development Corporation, 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Teaching and Historic Preservation 1997 (Box 27)
    - Miscellaneous Historic Preservation Materials, 2 folders (Box 27)
- Audio Materials
  The Audio Materials series contains audio cassettes dating from 1996-2003. These cassettes consist primarily of the testimony of various supporters of Historic Preservation in Ann Arbor
  - Audio Cassette Tapes
    - Sabra Briere Watts February 16, 2003 (Box 28)
    - Russell Bidlack February 20, 2001 (Box 28)
    - Lewis Bradford August 20, 2001 (Box 28)
    - Detter, Shackman, Pieper April 18, 2003 (Box 28)
    - Sally Kennedy November 7, 2001 (Box 28)
    - Sue Kosky March 21, 2004 (Box 28)
    - Mike Logghe October 19, 2003 (Box 28)
    - McCrary March 16, 2003 (Box 28)
    - Julie Creal Goodridge November 17, 2002 (Box 28)
    - Lorri Sipes September 20, 2003 (Box 28)
    - Pam Newhouse February 16, 2003 (Box 28)
    - Barry LaRue February 14, 2004 (microcassette) (Box 28)
    - Susan Wineberg December 4, 2003 (Box 28)
    - "Ann Arbor is a Better Place," 1996-1997 (Box 28)
  - Digital Materials
    - "The Greatest Gift," Calvary Chapel, Ann Arbor 2007 (Box 28)
- Visual Materials
  The Visual Materials series contains videotapes of public hearings of the Planning and Historic District Commissions from 1989-2000, a videotape about the Ann Arbor Historical Street Exhibit Program, photographs of historic properties, as well as related events and people, and 3 boxes of slides that document Ann Arbor historic properties and historic preservation activities.
  - Videotapes (VHS, T-120)
    - Ann Arbor City Council Public Hearings and Debates concerning Downtown Historic District Study Committee Proposals November 1989, December, 1989 (Box 28)
    - Ann Arbor Planning Commission Public Hearings concerning Individual Historic Properties Historic District Study Committee Proposals October 17, 1994 (Box 28)
    - Ann Arbor Historical Street Exhibit Program 2002 (Box 28)
    - Ann Arbor Historic District Commission, 300 Detroit St. and 112 W. Washington October, 1992 (Box 28)
    - Ann Arbor Historic District Commission June 8, 2000 (Box 28)
  - Photographs
    - 311 E. Ann Street (Box 28)
    - Book signing of Historical Buildings of Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1993 (Box 28)
      includes a picture of Susan Wineberg and Marjorie Reade
    - Individual Historic Properties Historic District Study Committee 1995 (Box 28)
    - Susan Wineberg's Poster in the "Libraries Change Lives" Exhibit 1996 (Box 28)
    - Historic Prints
      - Ann Arbor Buildings (Box 28)
      - Ann Arbor Store Fronts (Box 28)
      - Ann Arbor Transportation (most motor vehicles) (Box 28)
      - Ann Arbor People (Box 28)
    - Washtenaw County Historical Society, 150th Anniversary 2007 (Box 28)
      in 2 boxes
    - Detroit Zoo July 2007 (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous Ann Arbor 2005-2006 (Box 28)
      in 3 boxes
    - Zingerman's 25th Anniversary 2007 (Box 28)
    - Liberty Lofts and Old West Side Hometown 2006 (Box 28)
    - Weill Hall Dedication 2006 (Box 28)
    - Washtenaw County Historical Society 2007 (Box 28)
    - Frieze 2006 (Box 28)
    - Polhemas 2006 (Box 28)
    - Ann Arbor Historic Buildings, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Ann Arbor Landscapes (Box 28)
    - University of Michigan Buildings (Box 28)
    - Ann Arbor Street Scenes (Box 28)
    - Ann Arbor People (Box 28)
    - Ann Arbor Miscellaneous, 7 folders (Box 28)
  - Slides (35mm, color)
    - Ann Arbor Historic District Commission Awards Recipients 1987 (Box 29)
    - Old Fourth Ward Association Party 1993 (Box 29)
    - University of Michigan Anthropology Dept. students and faculty (Box 29)
    - Ann Arbor Historic Properties (Box 29)
    - Ann Arbor by street (Box 29)
      in 3 cases
    - Ann Arbor Various Topics (Box 29)
- Research / Reference files
  (include clippings, brochures, notes, and some slides)
  The Research / Reference files consists of clippings, published material, publicity brochures, notes, and some photographic slides that Susan Wineberg accumulated in the course of her research and interest in historic preservation. The file has been arranged into two principal subseries. The first - Michigan cities / counties -- includes most of the state except Ann Arbor, Detroit, and Washtenaw County. The second subseries documents Detroit, its history and buildings. The library has not yet received Wineberg's extensive file of Ann Arbor and University of Michigan material.
  - Michigan cities / counties
    (Ann Arbor, Detroit, and Washtenaw County not included)
    - Adrian (Box 4)
    - Albion (Box 4)
    - Alger County (Box 4)
    - Allegan County (Box 4)
    - Alpena (Box 4)
    - Antrim County (Box 4)
    - Barry County (Box 4)
    - Battle Creek (Box 4)
    - Bay City (Box 4)
    - Beaver Island (Box 4)
    - Belleville (Box 4)
    - Benton Harbor (Box 4)
    - Benzie County (Box 4)
    - Berrien County (Box 4)
    - Bloomfield Hills-Cranbrook (Box 4)
    - Branch County (Box 4)
    - Brighton (Box 4)
    - Calhoun County (Box 4)
    - Cass County (Box 4)
    - Charlevoix County (Box 4)
    - Chelsea (Box 4)
    - Dearborn (Box 4)
    - Dearborn -- Henry Ford Museum and Greenfield Village, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Drummond Island (Box 4)
    - East Lansing (Box 4)
    - Eaton County (Box 4)
    - Emmet County (Box 4)
    - Flint (Box 4)
    - Frankenmuth (Box 4)
    - Genesee County (Box 4)
    - Grand Rapids, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Grass Lake (Box 4)
    - Grosse Pointe -- Grosse Pointe Academy (Sacred Heart) (Box 4)
    - Grosse Pointe Park (Box 4)
    - Hamtramck (Box 4)
    - Highland Park (Box 4)
    - Hillsdale County (Box 4)
    - Holland (Box 4)
    - Huron County (Box 4)
    - Ingham County (Box 4)
    - Ionia County (Box 4)
    - Jackson County (Box 4)
    - Kalamazoo (Box 4)
    - Kent County (Box 4)
    - Lake County (Box 5)
    - Lansing (Box 5)
    - Lapeer County (Box 5)
    - Leelanau County (Box 5)
    - Lenawee County (Box 5)
    - Livingston County (Box 5)
    - Macomb County (Box 5)
    - Mackinac Island/Mackinaw City (Box 5)
    - Manistee County (Box 5)
    - Marquette County (Box 5)
    - Marshall, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Mason County (Box 5)
    - Mecosta County (Box 5)
    - Midland (Box 5)
    - Monroe County (Box 5)
    - Montcalm County (Box 5)
    - Mt. Clemens (Box 5)
    - Muskegon County (Box 5)
    - Newaygo County (Box 5)
    - Oceana County (Box 5)
    - Ottawa County (Box 5)
    - Petoskey (Box 5)
    - Pinckney (Box 5)
    - Plymouth (Box 5)
    - Pontiac (Box 5)
    - Presque Isle County (Box 5)
    - St. Clair County (Box 5)
    - St. Joseph County (Box 5)
    - Saginaw County (Box 5)
    - Sanilac County (Box 5)
    - Shiawassee County (Box 5)
    - Sault Ste. Marie (Box 5)
    - South Lyon (Box 5)
    - Tecumseh (Box 5)
    - Traverse City (Box 5)
    - Tuscola County (Box 5)
    - Upper Peninsula (Box 5)
    - Van Buren County (Box 5)
    - Wayne County (Box 5)
    - Western Michigan (Box 5)
    - Wexford County (Box 5)
    - Wyandotte (Box 5)
  - Detroit
    (Buildings/Areas/History)
    - Fabulous Ruins of Detroit (Box 6)
    - Detroit History (Box 6)
    - General (Box 6)
    - Specific Buildings (not already classified) (Box 6)
    - Apartments (Box 6)
    - Architects (Box 6)
    - Art Deco Buildings (Box 6)
    - Arts (Paintings, Furniture, etc.) (Box 6)
    - Automobile Related Buildings (Box 6)
    - Bed and Breakfasts (Box 6)
    - Belle Isle (Box 6)
    - Black Historic Sites (Box 6)
    - Book Building (Box 6)
    - Brush Park (Box 6)
    - Builders (Box 6)
    - Businesses (Box 6)
    - Casinos (Box 6)
    - Cemeteries (Box 6)
    - Churches (Box 6)
    - Clubs (Box 6)
      see also: Jazz Clubs
    - Cobo Hall (Box 6)
    - Comerica Park (Box 6)
    - Commercial Buildings (Box 6)
    - Detroit Athletic Club (Box 6)
    - Detroit Club (Box 6)
    - Detroit Fire Department Headquarters Building (Box 6)
    - Financial Buildings (Box 6)
    - Factories and Plants (Box 6)
    - First National Building (Box 6)
    - Fisher Building (Box 6)
    - Fisher Mansion (Box 6)
    - Fort Wayne (Box 6)
    - Fountains (Box 6)
      (see Sculpture, Fountains, and Architectural decoration)
    - Fox Theater (Box 6)
    - GM Building (Box 6)
    - Government Buildings (Box 6)
    - Guardian Building (Box 6)
    - Heidelberg Project (Box 6)
    - Historic Preservation (Box 6)
    - Hospitals/Medical Centers (Box 6)
    - Hotels (Box 6)
    - Houses (Box 7)
    - Houses (Historic), controversies (Box 7)
    - Hudson's, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Ilitch (Box 7)
    - Indian Village (Box 7)
    - Jazz Clubs (Box 7)
    - Libraries (Box 7)
    - Malls/Shopping Plazas (Box 7)
    - Markets (Box 7)
    - Masonic Temple (Box 7)
    - Michigan Central Railroad Station (Box 7)
    - Michigan Opera Theater (Box 7)
    - Monroe Block (Box 7)
    - Museums (Box 7)
    - Neighborhoods and Districts (Box 7)
    - Office Buildings (Box 7)
    - Orchestra Hall (Box 7)
    - One Detroit Center (Box 7)
    - Orchestra Hall (Box 7)
    - Parking Garages (Box 7)
    - Parks (Box 7)
    - Penobscot Building (Box 7)
    - Pewabic (Box 7)
    - Photographs and Photographers (Box 7)
    - Poletown (Box 7)
    - Rackham Building (Box 7)
    - Religious Buildings (Box 7)
      see also: Churches
    - Renaissance Center (Box 7)
    - Restaurants and Bars (Box 7)
    - Riverfront (Box 7)
    - Schools (Box 7)
    - Sculpture, Fountains, Architectural Decoration (Box 7)
    - Specific Buildings (Box 7)
    - Stadia (Box 7)
      (see also Comerica Park; Tiger Stadium)
    - Stores (Box 7)
    - Streets/Roads (Box 7)
    - Stroh's Project (Box 7)
    - Suburbs (Box 7)
    - Tiger Stadium, 2 folders (Box 7)
      (includes videotape)
    - Theaters (Box 8)
    - Transportation Buildings (Box 8)
    - Walking Tours (Box 8)
    - Wayne County Building (Box 8)
    - The Whitney (Box 8)
    - YMCA/YWCA (Box 8)
    - Slides and photographs of various Detroit landmark buildings (Box 8)
- Printed Ephemera and Realia
  The Printed Ephemera and Realia series includes such items as advertising materials, menus, business cards, political campaign materials of Ann Arbor candidates, programs, and other miscellanea. This series is arranged into two subseries: Detroit and Ann Arbor.
  - Detroit
    - Advertisements (on items) (Box 8)
    - Menus (Box 8)
    - Bags, Napkins, Stationary (Box 8)
    - Programs, Brochures, Flyers, 3 folders (Box 8)
    - Programs, Brochures, Flyers, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Reports and Articles, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Newsletters and Invitations (Box 9)
  - Ann Arbor
    - Ann Arbor artists and galleries (Box 9)
      (cards, calendars and flyers)
    - Ann Arbor businesses (Box 9)
      (cards, bookmarks, flyers)
    - Ann Arbor Film Festival (Box 10)
      (programs, flyers, posters, membership material)
    - Ann Arbor Film Festival realia (Box 10)
      (buttons, donor passes, temporary tattoos)
    - Ann Arbor Hands On Museum (Box 10)
      (newsletters, calendars, flyers)
    - Ann Arbor politics
      - Local and national political material (Box 10)
        (flyers, brochures, solicitation letters)
      - Perry Bullard, State Representative 53rd District 1976-1992 (Box 11)
        (brochures, reports, flyers)
    - Ann Arbor postcards (Box 11)
    - Ann Arbor Public Library (Box 11)
      (annual reports, bookmarks, bumper stickers, buttons, calendars, flyers, newsletters)
    - Blacks in Ann Arbor 1990s, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - City of Ann Arbor Publications (Box 11)
    - Domino's Pizza 1980s-1990s, 3 folders (Box 11)
    - Kerrytown Concert House (Box 11)
      (event calendars, flyers, programs)
    - Kerrytown Shops (Box 12)
      (flyers, guides, menus, reviews, slides)
    - Michigan Theatre donor and member materials (Box 12)
    - Michigan Theatre ephemera (event calendars, flyers, photos), 4 folders (Box 12)
    - Guides, flyers, menus, reviews (Box 13)
    - Campbell Family (Cobblestone Farm) (Box 13)
    - Churches (Box 13)
    - Ehnis love letters (Box 13)
    - Houses (306 E. Madison) (Box 13)
    - Lockwood Family photos (700, 800 Oxford) (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous portrait and group photos (Box 13)
    - Rosa Lueck (Box 13)
    - Schools (Box 13)
      (photos, postcards, negatives)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 13)
- Printed Ephemera and Realia 1969-2008
  The Printed Ephemera and Realia, 1969-2004 series includes advertising materials, menus, political materials, programs, brochures, flyers, and other miscellanea related to the history of Ann Arbor, Washtenaw County, and the state of Michigan.
  - Ann Arbor
    - Art Fair 2004-2007 (Box 30)
    - Calendars 1975-2008, 2 folders (Box 30)
      also oversize folder in Box 69
    - Miscellaneous Brochures and Flyers, 14 folders (Box 30)
    - Miscellaneous Brochures and Flyers, 4 folders (Box 31)
    - Miscellaneous Realia (Box 31)
    - New Housing (Box 31)
    - Politics (Box 31)
    - Postcards, 3 folders (Box 31)
    - Restaurants, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Summer Festival 2000-2008 (Box 31)
    - Zingerman's, 2 folders (Box 31)
  - Detroit
    - Miscellaneous Brochures and Flyers, 6 folders (Box 31)
      see also oversize folder in Box 69
    - Greenfield Village, The Henry Ford, and Cranbrook (Box 32)
    - University of Michigan, Dearborn (Box 32)
    - Fairlane: Henry Ford Estate (Box 32)
  - Michigan General
    - Michigan Public Interest Research Group (Box 32)
    - Miscellaneous Brochures and Flyers, 4 folders (Box 32)
      see also one oversize folder in Box 69
    - Postcards (Box 32)
- Collected Historical Materials
  The Collected Historical Materials series consists of a miscellanea of materials accumulated by Susan Wineberg, either purchased or given to her and having some connection with Ann Arbor, Washtenaw County, Detroit, the University of Michigan, or the state of Michigan.
  - Ann Arbor
    - Planned Parenthood of Mid-Michigan (Box 32)
    - Rulers (Box 32)
    - Michigan Abortion Rights Action League (MARAL) (Box 32)
    - Politics (Box 32)
    - Domino's Pizza (Box 32)
    - Realia (Box 32)
  - Ann Arbor
    - People (Box 33)
    - Blacks, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Jewish Community (Box 33)
    - Food, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Food, Culinary Historians (Box 33)
    - City Services (Box 33)
    - Couches on Porches 2004 (Box 33)
    - Hands on Museum (Box 33)
    - Art Fair (Box 33)
    - Artists (Box 33)
    - Michigan Theater, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Michigan Theater (Box 34)
    - Madstone/Briarwood (Box 34)
    - Ford Gallery (Box 34)
    - Photographers (Box 34)
    - Women's Clubs (Box 34)
    - Women (Box 34)
    - Bell Pool (Box 34)
    - R2B Task Force (Box 34)
    - Huron Plaza Conference Center (unbuilt) (Box 34)
    - Unbuilt Projects (Box 34)
    - Conference Center (Box 34)
    - Schools (Box 34)
    - Southwest Ann Arbor (Box 34)
    - Streets/Sidewalks (Box 34)
    - Southeast Ann Arbor (Box 34)
    - Television (Box 34)
    - Test of the Town (Box 34)
    - West Area Ann Arbor (Box 34)
    - Wystan Stevens, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Historic District Guidelines 2007 (Box 35)
    - Design Guidelines, AIA 2006 (Box 35)
    - Washtenaw County Stats (Box 35)
    - Calthorpe (Box 35)
    - Photographs First (Box 35)
    - Swain, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - State Theater (Box 35)
    - Film Festival, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Library (Box 36)
    - Classical Music (Box 36)
    - Music-Jazz (Box 36)
    - Music-Pop Folk (Box 36)
    - Kerrytown Concert House (Box 36)
    - Politics (Box 36)
    - Politics/City Government (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 36)
    - Advertising Cards (Box 36)
    - Airport (Box 36)
    - Antiques (Box 36)
    - Apartment Buildings (Box 36)
    - AIA Design Awards and Masonry Institute Awards (Box 36)
    - Blacks-History (Box 36)
    - Blacks 2005 (Box 37)
    - Business Miscellaneous (Box 37)
    - Historic Business Receipts 1900-1930s (Box 37)
    - Farmers Market (Box 37)
    - Film Group (Box 37)
    - Ann Arbor Garden Club (Box 37)
    - General Information/Statistics (Box 37)
    - Banks and Banking (Box 37)
    - University of Michigan Employees Credit Union (Box 37)
    - Ann Arbor Savings Bank 1869-1919 (Box 37)
    - Great Lakes Federal (Box 37)
    - Bank of Washtenaw and others (Box 37)
    - Parking (Box 37)
    - Libraries (Box 38)
    - Gandy Dancer Controversy 1975-1976, 2 folders (Box 38)
    - Arts of Citizenship (Box 38)
    - Hotels/Motels (Box 38)
    - Lower Town Background (Box 38)
    - Malls (Box 38)
    - Arborland (Box 38)
    - Briarwood Mall and Environs (Box 38)
    - Ann Arbor Newspapers (Box 38)
    - North Central Ann Arbor (Box 38)
    - Northeast Ann Arbor (Box 38)
    - Parks and Recreation (Box 38)
    - Postcards (Box 38)
    - Post Offices (Box 39)
    - Restaurant Menus (Box 39)
    - Infrastructure (Box 39)
    - Off to School 2000 (Box 39)
    - Books about Publishers (Box 39)
    - Bookstores (Box 39)
    - New Age Stuff (Box 39)
    - Miscellaneous Businesses (Box 39)
    - Politics, 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Jazz Music, 2 folders (Box 40)
    - Classical Music (Box 40)
    - Pop Music (Box 40)
    - Food, 2 folders (Box 40)
    - Restaurants (Box 40)
    - Culinary Symposia (Box 40)
    - Catering Menus (Box 40)
    - Art Association and Center (Box 41)
    - Art Fair, 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Washtenaw Council for Arts and other art organizations (Box 41)
    - Art Train (Box 41)
    - Artists (Box 41)
    - Summer Festival (Box 41)
    - Galleries, Selo/Shevel (Box 41)
    - Eskimo Art (Box 41)
    - Art Venues (Box 41)
    - 16 Hands (Box 41)
    - Simsar (Box 41)
    - Gallery One (Box 41)
    - Art Galleries and Art Walks (Box 41)
    - Restaurant Guides (Box 41)
    - Restaurant Coaster, Napkins, and Matchbooks (Box 41)
    - Restaurants, Miscellaneous (Box 41)
    - Zingerman's (Box 41)
    - Grocery Stores
      - Arbor Farms (Box 41)
      - Kroger (Box 42)
      - Produce Station, Meijer, Whole Foods, Busch's, and Hiller's (Box 42)
    - Food Products (Box 42)
    - Food Stores Miscellaneous (Box 42)
    - Food Stores, Complete Cuisine/Kitchen Port/Kerrytown/Food Co-op (Box 42)
    - Planned Parenthood (Box 42)
    - Political Rallies (Box 42)
    - Washtenaw United Way (Box 42)
    - Environmental Issues/Health Issues (Box 42)
    - Appliance Stores (Box 42)
    - Aristoplay (Box 42)
    - Building Trades/Realtors (Box 42)
    - Cars (Box 42)
    - Clothing Stores (Box 42)
    - Date Books (Giveaways) (Box 42)
    - Department Stores, Goodyear's/Jacobson's (Box 42)
    - Dry Cleaners (Box 42)
    - Urban Outfitters (Box 42)
    - Drugstores (Box 42)
    - Fitness/Sports (Box 42)
    - Furniture Stores (Box 42)
    - Gift Stores (Box 42)
    - Hair and Beauty (Box 42)
    - Hardware (Box 42)
    - Hotels/Motels (Box 42)
    - Insurance Companies (Box 42)
    - Jewelers (Box 42)
    - Music (Box 42)
    - Paint Stores (Box 42)
    - Printing/Graphics/Copying (Box 42)
    - Medical (Box 42)
    - Photography (Box 42)
    - Shoes (Box 42)
    - Snow Removal (Box 42)
    - Video Stores (Box 42)
    - District Library (Box 43)
    - For the People 1991-1994 (Box 43)
    - Ann Arbor Transportation Authority (AATA), 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Public and Private Schools (Box 43)
    - Washtenaw Community College (Box 43)
    - City Departments (Box 43)
    - TV-CTN, Community Access (Box 43)
    - Parking (Box 43)
    - Police (Box 43)
    - Parks and Recreation, 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Bicycle Stuff (Box 43)
    - Neighborhood Senior Services (Box 43)
    - Antiques (Box 43)
    - Miscellaneous Michigan (Box 43)
    - Dance (Box 43)
    - Miscellaneous Music (Box 43)
    - Business
      - Nickels Arcade (Box 43)
      - Business Cards 1980s-1990s (Box 43)
      - Kerrytown (Box 44)
      - Renaissance Clothing 1970s-2000s (Box 44)
      - Bookstores (Box 44)
      - Briarwood/Arborland (Box 44)
      - Gardens and Plants (Box 44)
      - Main Street Merchants Association (Box 44)
      - State Street Merchants Association (Box 44)
      - Chamber of Commerce and Convention and Visitors' Center (Box 44)
    - Animal Rescue and Veterinarians (Box 44)
    - Hands on Museum (Box 44)
    - Non-Profits (Box 44)
    - Miscellaneous Ann Arbor (Box 44)
    - Politics 1980s-1990s (Box 44)
    - Politics 1980s-1990s (Box 45)
    - Politics, Shackman, Rivers, Brater (Box 45)
    - Political Memorabilia (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous Businesses 1980s-1990s (Box 45)
    - Business Coupon Books 1990s (Box 45)
    - Jewish Organizations (Box 45)
    - University of Michigan Food (Box 45)
    - University of Michigan Medical (Box 45)
    - Menus (Box 45)
    - Coffee and Coffee Shops (Box 45)
    - Pizza Menus (Box 45)
    - Michigan Theater/Movie Theaters (Box 46)
    - Film Festival (Box 46)
    - Kerrytown Concert House (Box 46)
    - The Ark (Box 46)
    - Young People's Theater/Wild Swan (Box 46)
    - Civic Theater (Box 46)
    - Performance Network (Box 46)
    - Theaters-Various (Box 46)
    - Comedy Showcase (Box 46)
    - Summer Festival (Box 46)
    - Symphony (Box 46)
    - Jazz and Blue's Festival 1985-2009 (scattered) (Box 46)
    - Chamber Arts/Ars Musica/Cantata Singers (Box 46)
    - Folk Festival 1970, 1990, 1996 (Box 46)
    - Papagena Opera/Comic Opera/Strelstra (Box 46)
    - Popular Music (Box 46)
    - Music Clubs (Box 46)
    - Medieval Festival 1981-1984, undated (Box 46)
    - Food (Box 46)
    - 809 Brooks Street (Box 46)
    - Miscellaneous 1960s Flyers (Box 46)
    - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 46)
  - Ypsilanti
    - Heritage Foundation (Box 47)
    - Heritage News (Box 47)
    - Historical Society Calendars (Box 47)
    - Historic Buildings by name (Box 47)
    - History (Box 47)
    - Maps (Box 47)
    - Museums (Box 47)
    - People (Box 47)
    - Restaurants (Box 47)
    - Schools (Box 47)
    - Water Tower (Box 47)
    - Memorabilia, Ephemera, and Pictures (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 47)
    - Auto History (Box 47)
    - Businesses (Box 47)
    - Blacks (Box 47)
    - Cemeteries (Box 47)
    - Churches (Box 47)
    - Depot Town (Box 47)
    - Directory 1879 (Box 47)